https://www.sentranllc.com/privacy.htm

Home
»
Privacy
Sentran, LLC Data Privacy PolicyProtecting the security and privacy of your personal data is important to Sentran, LLC. Therefore, the Sentran, LLC Corporation referred to under “Corporate Information” (“Sentran, LLC”) operates its website(s) in compliance with applicable laws on data privacy protection and data security.In the following, we provide information on the kinds of data we collect on these Sentran, LLC website(s), the purposes for which we use such data, and the parties with which we share such data, where applicable. Collected Data and Purpose of Processing Sentran, LLC may store some information (commonly known as a "cookie") on your computer when you visit this website which thereafter may be read for information purposes upon any subsequent visits to this website. The cookie information is utilized to improve Sentran, LLC's knowledge of the use of this website and enables Sentran, LLC to ascertain whether the website is operating at an optimal level. This allows Sentran, LLC to enhance and customize its website services to you. You can erase or block this information by changing the settings on your computer.On some pages of the website Sentran, LLC may allow you to make requests or send email which will require certain personal information to be provided to Sentran, LLC. The types of personal information that may be collected at these pages include your name, name of company, address, telephone number, fax number and email address. Sentran, LLC may use the information provided to complete your request. Sentran, LLC will not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete the request or as otherwise provided herein. Sentran, LLC may use your email address to respond to any inquiry you submit or to alert you to product announcements. In addition, Sentran, LLC may use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that "X" number of individuals visited a certain area on this website.Sentran, LLC may disclose any information we have about you (including your identity) if we determine that such disclosure is necessary in connection with any investigation or complaint regarding your use of the website, or to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Sentran, LLC's rights or property, or the rights or property of visitors to or users of the website. Sentran, LLC reserves the right at all times to disclose any information that Sentran, LLC deems necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. Sentran, LLC also may disclose your information when Sentran, LLC determines that applicable law requires or permits such disclosure, including exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection purposes.Accesses to our website are logged for the purpose of security analysis reports and to defend against cyber-attacks. With the exception of the IP address, no personal data is ever collected or used in this connection. IP addresses are analyzed only in the event of a cyber-attack.In addition, we collect personal data (e.g., names, addresses, telephone numbers, or e-mail addresses) in connection with the operation of our websites only when you have voluntarily provided such data to us (e.g., through registration, contact inquiries, surveys, etc.) and when we are entitled to process or use such data by virtue of permission granted by you or on the basis of a statutory provision.As a general rule, we use such data only for the purpose for which you divulged the data to us, such as to answer your inquiries, process your orders, or grant you access to certain information or offerings. Sharing of DataInsofar as you have provided your consent or when we are otherwise legally entitled to do so, we will share your personal data with subsidiaries of Sentran, LLC, where applicable, for the purposes indicated above.In connection with the operation of its website and the services provided by way of the website, Sentran, LLC works with service providers such as hosting or IT maintenance service providers, for example.These recipients may possibly be located in countries outside of the United States of America, in which applicable laws do not offer the same level of data privacy protection as in your home country. In such cases, Sentran, LLC takes measures to ensure an appropriate level of data privacy protection. For example, we share your personal data with Sentran, LLC subsidiaries in other countries only if they have implemented our rules for the protection of personal data. Data is shared only in connection with and in compliance with applicable laws and regulations. We do not sell or otherwise market your personal data to third parties. Questions and Comments; ChangesSentran, LLC will respond to all legitimate requests for information and where applicable, to correct, amend, or delete your personal data. If you wish to make such a request or if you have questions or comments about this Data Privacy Policy, please click on the “Contact” link to send us your questions and suggestions.This Data Privacy Policy is updated from time to time, without notice.
Helpful Links
Request a Quote
Datasheets
Support
Application Worksheets
Industry Resources
Digital Catalog
Products
Toll-Free: 888-545-8988|P:
909-605-1544|F: 909-605-6305|support@sentranllc.com|www.sentranllc.com
Copyright Sentran LLC
2020. All Rights Reserved.
Website Design by
Hudson
